[{"question": " hey guys!", "answer": " hey, let me tell them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " sure.", "answer": " joey is gonna be a celebrity guest on a game show!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " great!", "answer": " really? which one?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  ohh! fish, seaweed, a sunken ship.", "answer": " things you find in the ocean,  you're gonna be on &quot;pyramid&quot;!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " oh, that was our favourite game show ever!", "answer": " except for &quot;match game&quot;...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " or &quot;win, lose or draw&quot;.", "answer": " what did i marry into?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " would you guys want to come down tomorrow and watch me tape the show?", "answer": " oh, i can't. we're throwing phoebe a bachelorette party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " yeah, sorry boys, this ride's closing.", "answer": " oh, and chandler and i have this stupid college alumni thing. i can't believe you get to meet donny osmond.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " seriously?", "answer": "  yeah-uh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " ross and i always wanted to be donny and marie.", "answer": " you guys just keep getting cooler and cooler!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " yeah, we used to perform for our family and friends.", "answer": " oh god, that's right. i blocked that out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  &quot;i'm a little bit country&quot;...", "answer": "  &quot;...and i'm a little bit rock 'n' roll&quot;!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " so weird to see all these people again... oh my god, look, there's geoffrey cleric.", "answer": " who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " he was roommates with john rosoff. he went out with andrea tamburino. she dumped him for michael skloff.", "answer": "  did i go to this school?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " hey, there's missy goldberg. you gotta remember her.", "answer": "  sure, nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " dude. you're married to my sister.", "answer": " you're right, by saying &quot;nice&quot; i'm virtually licking her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hey, i hear she's single again, d'you think i should ask her out?", "answer": " are you asking permission to break the pact?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " hey. hey, check out the flyers for the band. i made 'em on a macintosh in the computer room!", "answer": " awesome, the name really stands out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " thanks to a little something called &quot;helvetica bold 24 point&quot;!", "answer": " man, we're gonna rock that asian student union!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey guys!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hey, missy...", "answer": " you know, our band is playing on friday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " yeah, yeah. you should come check us out. we're called &quot;way! no way!&quot;.", "answer": " no way! chandler and ross: way!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " fresh!", "answer": " boss!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " mint!", "answer": " she's gone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " i know it. you know, i'm totally gonna ask her out.", "answer": " dude, i was gonna ask her out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " i said it first, bro.", "answer": " well, i thought it first, holmes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  look, if you did...", "answer": " woha! wait... what are we doing? what we have is too important to mess it up over some girl. i mean, we can get laid anytime we want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " totally. i had sex in high school...", "answer": " me too. i'm good at it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " all right, i'd say we make a pact. neither of us will go out with missy goldberg.", "answer": " you got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " all right, so that's missy goldberg, phoebe cates and molly ringwald, who neither of us can go out with.", "answer": " those are the pacts!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh, and sheena easton. but we probably couldn't get her anyway.", "answer": " oh, oh... maybe not you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " well, i officially give you permission to break the pact.", "answer": " thank you.  all right, here i go. hey, remember how scary it used to be going up to girls in college?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " your hands are shaking.", "answer": " i know, and i can't stop sweating.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " five! four! three! applause!", "answer": " yeah! welcome, it is soap opera week here on pyramid, let's meet our contestants. first, gene lester is a database specialist, he's gonna be playing with &quot;days of our life's&quot; star joey tribbiani!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  i know it could be intimidating for regular people to be around celebrities but... relax, i'm just like you!  only better looking and richer.", "answer": " ...should be playing with the star of &quot;general hospital&quot; leslie charleson.  welcome everybody. good luck to all of you. let's play pyramid. all right? now... we flipped a coin before the show, gene, you won the toss, so you're gonna start. which category would you like?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " i'll take &quot;you crossed the line&quot;.", "answer": " you crossed the line. joey, describe for gene these things that have lines. give me 20 seconds on the clock, please. ready, go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": "  uhm... ok. it's a store, like a supermarket.  oh! i see-i see what i did. yeah, ok, ok, uhm... i'm writing in my...", "answer": " diary.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " noo,  more like a notebook... damn it!  oh, if i'm building an house, the plan isn't called the 'shmoo-print'... can't say that either? woha... hey...  in high school, i once had sex with a girl right in the middle of the...", "answer": " cafeteria.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": "  thank you so much for this.", "answer": " oh, d'you like it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh my god, it's all so elegant! when's the dirty stuff starting?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " you know, the strippers, and the guys dancing, and you know, pee-pee's flying about.", "answer": " pheebs, i... there isn't gonna be any flying about! we actually thought we were a little too mature for stuff like that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " oh, ok. i see what you're doing, that's fine. this is all there is, just tea, uh, ok.  hmmmm... raunchy!", "answer": " seriously pheebs, it's not gonna be that kind of a party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " really? so this is... this is my big send off in the married life? rachel this is the only bachelorette party i'm ever gonna have! i've got a big wad of ones in my purse! really? i mean, really? it's just tea?", "answer": " nooo! phoebe, of course there is more! i mean, i'll just go and talk to monica and get an eta on the pee-pee's!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " now gene i must remind you, you need all six of these to stay in the game, all right? describe for joey things you find in your refrigerator.", "answer": " ahaha, he might as well just give us the points.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " you put this in your coffee.", "answer": " a spoon. your hands. your face!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " it's white!", "answer": " paper, snow, a ghost!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " it's heavier then milk!", "answer": " a rock, a dog, the earth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " you put this on a sandwich.", "answer": " salami, anchovies, jam!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " it's white!", "answer": " paper, snow, a ghost!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " it's made from eggs!", "answer": " chickens?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " pass!", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " you put this on a hamburger!", "answer": " ketchup!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " relish!", "answer": " stop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " oh, time's up! joey! you were, uh, almost on a roll there...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah...", "answer": " uh, gene, you're gonna have a chance to go to the winner circle in the second half. but right now henrietta you are going to the winner circle to try your luck for ten thousand dollars, right after this, don't go away. stage manager : and we're out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh, so we didn't win, but it's fun to play the game, right?", "answer": " hey! i got a kid starting college. i've to get surgery on my knee, you just lost me ten grand!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " oh, wow! i'm so sorry, ok? i promise, we'll do better next time!", "answer": " well, i will, because i won't be playing with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " so, saturday night!", "answer": " i'd love to!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " great!", "answer": " so how come it took you so long to ask me out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " oh, well, uh, this is gonna sound kinda silly, but, do you remember my roommate chandler bing?", "answer": " sure, he was in your &quot;band&quot;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " it's been sixteen years but the air quotes still hurt.", "answer": " sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " that's ok. uh, anyway, well he and i both really liked you a lot, uhm, but we didn't want anything to jeopardize our friendship, so we kinda made a pact, that neither of us could ask you out!", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " yeah, why?", "answer": " well, chandler and i used to make out! a lot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " you did?", "answer": " yeah. we'd go to the science lab after hours!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  hey, where is this guy, it's been over an hour!", "answer": " well, he's coming from jersey, he said he would get here as fast as he could!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " who is it?", "answer": " it's the police!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  uh! the police!", "answer": "  oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " that's right, it's officer goodbody.", "answer": " what's the matter, officer? has someone been bad?  roy, the male stripper:  whoo, that's a lot of stairs! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " ooh, boy. you should warn people there's no elevator! i should not have had that mexican food for lunch.", "answer": " are you gonna be ok, officer, uhm,...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " goodbody!", "answer": " ...if-you-say-so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh, god!", "answer": " all right, somebody show me where to plug in my box, and we'll get this party started!  whaaaa...  here? all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " rachel?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " are you kidding?", "answer": " all right, look, we did not know that you wanted a stripper so we went to the phonebook and we got the first name we could find!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " how old is your phonebook?", "answer": " oh my god, this man is gonna get naked in my apartment!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " oh god no, i don't wanna see him take his clothes off!", "answer": " are you talking about me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh, no! i mean, obviously we want to see you take your clothes off! you big piece of eye candy!", "answer": " ok, ok, ladies! can i have your attention, please?  did someone call for the long arm of the law?  i should warn you, i have a concealed weapon!  i hope you're familiar with the states penal code, ok, ok, enough teasing. now for some pleasing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " whoa, whoa, whoa . she cringed!", "answer": " this is how i look when i'm turned on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " you were talking about me before! look, i don't need this! i'm outta here! where's my hat?  look, i've been in this business for a long time!", "answer": " shocking!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " now if you just pay me my three hundred dollars, i'll be on my way!", "answer": " three hundred dollars, are you kidding?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " no, that's ok, let's me just get my check book!", "answer": " no, you're not gonna pay him, he didn't do anything!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " didn't do anything? i took a bus all the way from hoboken. i climbed ... i dunno... like a billion stairs... it's not like i can take them two at a time!", "answer": " i don't care. we're not paying you 300 dollars for this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " well, look - it's not my fault if you're too uptight to appreciate the male form in all it's glory.", "answer": " oh yeah, okay. i'm uptight. yeah, that's why i don't want to watch a middle aged guy dance around in what i can only assume is a child halloween costume!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " i may have borrowed this from my nephew, but let me assure you, what's underneath ... is all man.", "answer": " i'm sorry, did you say all man or old man?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": "  oh, you're mean!", "answer": "  uh, look, officer... uhm sir...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " ok henrietta, you've picked jack and jill went up the hill.", "answer": "  my friend rachel has a kid. i totally know nursery rhymes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " oh, .. uh... uh... pass.  pass.  pass.   okay, the little thing that hangs down at the back of your throat.", "answer": " uvula!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  excuse me. . that didn't make us sound gay at all!", "answer": " you broke the pact!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " ross, that was 16 years ago!", "answer": " that doesn't matter! we're talking about the foundation of our friendship.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " i believe the foundation of our friendship was unfortunate hair.  all right, look, if we're really gonna do this... it's not like you never broke one of the pacts.", "answer": " i didn't.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " oh really?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh really!?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " i never did anything with adrienne turner.", "answer": " oh please, and you knew how much i liked her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " i don't know what... you're talking about.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " i can't believe we are at a real college party!  i have to pee so bad!", "answer": " this is so awesome! college guys are so cute!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " hey, you've got a boyfriend!", "answer": " i know. but if some guy who looks like corey haim wants to kiss me tonight, i'm sooo gonna let them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " look, there's chandler. you knew, that stupid friend of ross'. said i'm fat. you know i've already lost 4 pounds!", "answer": " it... you can so totally tell.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " i know!", "answer": " well lets see. maybe he knows where ross is.  hey, how's it going .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " aren't you...?", "answer": " yeah, rachel. and this  is ross' sister, monica. we met at thanksgiving. .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": "  right.  so how're you doing?", "answer": " bitchin'", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " hi monica.", "answer": " hi chandler. it's really nice to see you  not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " oh my god rach. bean bag chairs.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " listen adrienne, you can't tell chandler about this.", "answer": " oh believe me, ross, i won't be telling anybody about this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " i didn't know you knew about that.", "answer": " well, i did and it hurt.  that's when i wrote the song: &quot;betrayal in the common room&quot;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  man... i... i'm sorry.", "answer": " look  it was a lo-o-ong time ago.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " so, eh. i made out with adrienne and you made out with missy. well i guess we're even.", "answer": "  hmm mmmhm..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " we are even, right?", "answer": "  just one more thing. i was so pissed at you that night that i wanted to get back at you. so i thought, who does ross like the more than anybody?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": "  what did you do to my mom?", "answer": " not her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " i am sooo drunk.", "answer": " that's weird. i've had the same number of beers as you and i don't feel anything at all.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " soo... you girls having fun?", "answer": " for your information, ass munch, i've lost four pounds. maybe even five with all the dancing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " somebody order a pizza?", "answer": " oh thats me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": "  i am soo not going to do good on my sats tomorrow.", "answer": " well maybe if you go to school here next year we can totally hang out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": "  oh yeah. there is a plan! why don't i just start taking my smart pills now?", "answer": " well, maybe you can get in on a beauty scholarship.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " so where are you applying to?", "answer": " oh well, you know, i think it's kinda really important that i go somewhere where there's sun, so i'm sort of...   hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " i'm in college and i'm in a band.", "answer": "  yeah okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " what's the matter? you never saw a 50 year old stripper cry before?", "answer": " you know, it's fine. we'll pay you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " no, no, you're right. who am i kidding? i should have hung up that breakaway jockstrap years ago. what am i gonna do? i mean, this has been my life for thirty two years. taking my clothes off in front of people is all i know.", "answer": " no, wait. no there's gotta be something else that you can do. i mean, what skills do you have?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " i don't know... i can make my pecs dance... i can pick up a dollar bill with my butt cheeks... i can go to that special place inside me where i feel no shame.", "answer": " so maybe something in an office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " or you could teach stripping. you know, share your gift, pass the torch.", "answer": " you know, actually that's not a bad idea. i can do it out of my apartment. i don't think my mom would mind.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " there you go. okay, do you think you're gonna be okay?", "answer": " yeah, yeah, yeah... this is so weird. i mean, you never know when it's gonna be your last dance. and i didn't even get a chance to finish it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": "  finish it!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " your last dance. do it for us.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": "  really?", "answer": " yeah, yeah. he deserves to do the thing he loves one last time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " oh no, no, no, don't stop!", "answer": "  have to...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " well, welcome to the winner circle. joey and gene, you guys ready?", "answer": "  yeah...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " oak, maple, elm, birch...", "answer": " i-i-i don't know. types of trees?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " uhm... buenos d&iacute;as, enchilada, por favor...", "answer": "  oh, i'm so sorry. i don't know any spanish words.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " a match, a candle...", "answer": " things that go &quot;tssst&quot; when you put them out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " a torch, a bonfire...  uhm, your pee...", "answer": " things that burn.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " &quot;i'd like to go for a walk&quot;, uhm &quot;scratch my belly&quot;.", "answer": " dude, dude! i think you're losing it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " uhm, &quot;i have fur&quot;, &quot;i like to bark&quot;.", "answer": " oh, oh, oh... what a dog says.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " pepperoni...", "answer": "  pizza toppings, next!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}, {"question": " cindy crawford, christie brinkley, heidi klum, claudia schiffer...", "answer": " oh, oh, oh...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " christie turlington, kate moss...", "answer": " girls chandler could never get?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 317, "asentId": 318}, {"question": "  supermodels!", "answer": " where?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 319, "asentId": 320}, {"question": " hey, where's rachel?", "answer": " she and phoebe took the stripper to the hospital.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " did you know chandler kissed rachel?", "answer": " what? when was this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}, {"question": " nineteen eighty seven. the weekend you guys visited me at school.", "answer": " oh my god! that's wild!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 325, "asentId": 326}, {"question": " yeah, but it was like a million years ago, so it doesn't matter.", "answer": " well, it matters to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " because... the night you kissed rachel was the night i kissed rachel for the very first time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 329, "asentId": 330}, {"question": " you kissed her that night too?", "answer": " two guys in one night? wow, i thought she became a slut after she got her nose fixed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 331, "asentId": 332}, {"question": " seriously, where did this happen?", "answer": " okay, after you told me she was passed out in our room, i went in there to make sure she was all right. she was lying on my bed, all buried in peoples coats. well, i went to kiss her on the forehead, you know. but it was so dark, i accidentally got her lips. i started to pull away, but then i felt her start to kiss me back. it was only for a second, but... it was amazing. and now, now i find out that you kissed her first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 333, "asentId": 334}, {"question": " oh wait... what bed did you say she was on?", "answer": " mine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 335, "asentId": 336}, {"question": " i'm pretty sure i put her on my bed.", "answer": " no, she was definitely on my bed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 337, "asentId": 338}, {"question": " why would i kiss a girl, and then put her on your bed?", "answer": " well, then who was on my bed?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 339, "asentId": 340}, {"question": "  no! no, no!", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 343, "asentId": 344}, {"question": " you were under the pile of coats?", "answer": " i was the pile of coats!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 345, "asentId": 346}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " you were my midnight mystery kisser?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 347, "asentId": 348}, {"question": " you were my first kiss with rachel?", "answer": " you were my first kiss ever?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s10/ep11.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 349, "asentId": 350}]